nileair.com 2012-05-30

# Privacy Policy

   **Nile Air** is committed to protecting the privacy of information you provide us on this website.

   This policy explains how we collect and use customer information and how we protect your

   privacy.

  This policy is applicable to Nile Air website only and does not cover any access you make to

   third party sites, even while using links from our Nile Air website.

 **  1\. Why do we ask for personal information?**

 **  2\. How do we use your personal information?**

 **  3\. Disclosure of your personal information**

 **  4\. Cookies**

 **  5\. Site tracking**

 **  6\. Security**

 **  7\. Consent**

 **  1\. Why do we ask for personal information?**

 ****  
    The personal information we request is necessary to allow us to process your flight booking. It is

   also required to register you on our website. Such information includes but not limited to: name,

   family names, mailing addresses, telephone numbers, email addresses, billing addresses, credit

   or debit card numbers, expiry dates and security numbers.

      If you are making a booking on behalf of another person, make sure that you have gained their

   consent to divulge such information. It is possible that such information may be globally processed.

 **  2\. How do we use your personal information?**

 ****  
    Our airline will use your information to provide and personalise our service. We will also use your 

   contact details to communicate with you. We may use your information to send you offers, travel

   deals and news about Nile Airproducts and services or those of relevant companies which we

   think may be of interest to you. We may contact you by post, email, telephone (including SMS) or

   fax for these purposes. We may also use and analyse the information that we collect so that we 

   can review, administer, support, improve and develop our business and the services which we offer.

 **  3\. Disclosure of your personal information**

 ****  
    Nile Air will not share or trade your personal information to third parties unless in case of emergency

   or when required by law.

   Nile Air may only share your personal information to the extent required for the performance of 

   activities such as: making an air travel reservation; recording and issuing a ticket; issuing a

   boarding pass; other purposes associated with or incidental to your carriage [Conditions of Carriage];

   in order to facilitate related transactions to your journey such as car hire or hotel accommodation; 

   to customs and/or immigration departments or other regulatory authorities in your country of departure

   and/or destination in order to comply with the law in those countries; and to our employees and 

   agents to execute any of the above on our behalf.

 **  4\. Cookies**

 ****  
    A ‘cookie’ is a small bit of data used by a browser to store information. These enable Nile Air to 

   provide you with more personalized service on any future bookings. Cookies can be deleted from 

   your hard drive if you wish. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can change

   your browser settings to prevent that option. Even without a cookie you can use most of the features

   on our website. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information.

 **  5\. Site Tracking**

 ****  
    We use tracking software to monitor customer traffic patterns and site usage to help us develop the

   design and layout of our website. This software does not enable us to capture any personally

   identifying information.

 **  6\. Security**

   We take great care to ensure the security of this site. Nile Air uses 128-bit Secure Socket Layer (SSL) 

   web technology to encrypt all shared data. This means that all your personal information and credit card

    numbers are protected while it is being sent over the Internet.

 **  7\. Consent**

 ****  
    In using the Nile Air website, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Nile Airi n the 

   ways described above. If you have any further questions about our Privacy Policy or its implementation,

    please contact our customer relations department.
